[
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove a password , say:",
    "options": [
      "Log out the password",
      "Go jogging",
      "Hurry back",
      "Move out furniture"
    ],
    "answer": "Log out the password"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove the name , say:",
    "options": [
      "Improve",
      "Get some rest",
      "Take off makeup",
      "Cross off the name"
    ],
    "answer": "Cross off the name"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove a sticker , say:",
    "options": [
      "Get some rest",
      "Peel off the sticker",
      "Go outside",
      "Make an effort"
    ],
    "answer": "Peel off the sticker"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove makeup , say:",
    "options": [
      "Complete homework",
      "Take off makeup",
      "Prepare",
      "Have lunch"
    ],
    "answer": "Take off makeup"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove stains , say:",
    "options": [
      "Wipe off stains",
      "Clean up",
      "Tease",
      "Move out furniture"
    ],
    "answer": "Wipe off stains"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove the lid , say:",
    "options": [
      "Sign",
      "Wash off dirt",
      "Pop off the lid",
      "Take a test"
    ],
    "answer": "Pop off the lid"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove shoes , say:",
    "options": [
      "Repeat the mistake",
      "Clean up",
      "Slip off shoes",
      "Draw a sketch"
    ],
    "answer": "Slip off shoes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove the dirt , say:",
    "options": [
      "Get some rest",
      "Wash off dirt",
      "Make a decision",
      "Have fun"
    ],
    "answer": "Wash off dirt"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove paint , say:",
    "options": [
      "Scrape off paint",
      "Discuss",
      "Set off",
      "File a complaint"
    ],
    "answer": "Scrape off paint"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove dust , say:",
    "options": [
      "Take off clothes",
      "Plan",
      "Brush off the dust",
      "Speak up"
    ],
    "answer": "Brush off the dust"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove the nail , say:",
    "options": [
      "Give news",
      "Repeat the mistake",
      "Brush off the dust",
      "Pull out the nail"
    ],
    "answer": "Pull out the nail"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove furniture , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make a decision",
      "Give news",
      "Move out furniture",
      "Have breakfast"
    ],
    "answer": "Move out furniture"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove garbage , say:",
    "options": [
      "Act",
      "Take out the garbage",
      "Apologize",
      "Have a rest"
    ],
    "answer": "Take out the garbage"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove a bandage , say:",
    "options": [
      "Pull off the bandage",
      "Have breakfast",
      "Make arrangements",
      "Perform duty"
    ],
    "answer": "Pull off the bandage"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do a decision , say:",
    "options": [
      "Start work",
      "Go swimming",
      "Throw a party",
      "Make a decision"
    ],
    "answer": "Make a decision"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do a mistake , say:",
    "options": [
      "Hurry back",
      "Meditate",
      "Make a mistake",
      "Go outside"
    ],
    "answer": "Make a mistake"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do an effort , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make an effort",
      "Slip off shoes",
      "File a complaint",
      "Start work"
    ],
    "answer": "Make an effort"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Say an apology , say:",
    "options": [
      "Show interest",
      "Improve",
      "Wash off dirt",
      "Apologize"
    ],
    "answer": "Apologize"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Say a lie , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make a decision",
      "React",
      "Tell a lie",
      "Become friends"
    ],
    "answer": "Tell a lie"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Say news , say:",
    "options": [
      "Go shopping",
      "Make a mistake",
      "Log out the password",
      "Give news"
    ],
    "answer": "Give news"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take a rest , say:",
    "options": [
      "Repeat the mistake",
      "Invest",
      "Have a rest",
      "Take an exam"
    ],
    "answer": "Have a rest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take food , say:",
    "options": [
      "Go outside",
      "Take out the garbage",
      "Grab food",
      "Take off clothes"
    ],
    "answer": "Grab food"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Make clean , say:",
    "options": [
      "Arrive at the office",
      "Clean up",
      "Have a rest",
      "Take medicine"
    ],
    "answer": "Clean up"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Make fast , say:",
    "options": [
      "Slip off shoes",
      "Run a business",
      "Move out furniture",
      "Speed up"
    ],
    "answer": "Speed up"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Stop working , say:",
    "options": [
      "Start work",
      "Arrive at the office",
      "Show interest",
      "Shut down (a machine)"
    ],
    "answer": "Shut down (a machine)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Start a journey , say:",
    "options": [
      "Act",
      "Perform duty",
      "Complete homework",
      "Set off"
    ],
    "answer": "Set off"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Start talking , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make a mistake",
      "Speak up",
      "Ask for help",
      "Perform duty"
    ],
    "answer": "Speak up"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Look carefully , say:",
    "options": [
      "Check out / Look over",
      "React",
      "Book (a seat, hotel, etc.)",
      "Pop off the lid"
    ],
    "answer": "Check out / Look over"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Look angrily , say:",
    "options": [
      "Meditate",
      "Glare at",
      "Make a decision",
      "Grab food"
    ],
    "answer": "Glare at"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Look secretly , say:",
    "options": [
      "Scrape off paint",
      "Worry",
      "Hang up",
      "Peek at"
    ],
    "answer": "Peek at"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Look quickly , say:",
    "options": [
      "Glance at",
      "Arrive at the office",
      "Attend an interview",
      "Take off clothes"
    ],
    "answer": "Glance at"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Get knowledge , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make a mistake",
      "Slip off shoes",
      "Learn",
      "Sign"
    ],
    "answer": "Learn"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Make it ready , say:",
    "options": [
      "Show interest",
      "Prepare",
      "Shut down (a machine)",
      "Peel off the sticker"
    ],
    "answer": "Prepare"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Make quiet , say:",
    "options": [
      "Wash off dirt",
      "Register",
      "Calm down",
      "Make a phone call"
    ],
    "answer": "Calm down"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Open the light , say:",
    "options": [
      "Turn on the light",
      "Cross off the name",
      "Worry",
      "Go outside"
    ],
    "answer": "Turn on the light"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Close the light , say:",
    "options": [
      "Take a picture",
      "Turn off the light",
      "Take a test",
      "Make progress"
    ],
    "answer": "Turn off the light"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Make a photo , say:",
    "options": [
      "Build a relationship",
      "Ask for help",
      "Hurry back",
      "Take a photo"
    ],
    "answer": "Take a photo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do a mistake , say:",
    "options": [
      "Invest",
      "Make a mistake",
      "Cheat or Copy",
      "Hurry back"
    ],
    "answer": "Make a mistake"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do homework , say:",
    "options": [
      "Complete homework",
      "Show interest",
      "Come inside",
      "Scrape off paint"
    ],
    "answer": "Complete homework"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Eat medicine , say:",
    "options": [
      "Go swimming",
      "Take a picture",
      "Wipe off stains",
      "Take medicine"
    ],
    "answer": "Take medicine"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: See a dream , say:",
    "options": [
      "Have a dream",
      "Meditate",
      "Move out furniture",
      "Take a photo"
    ],
    "answer": "Have a dream"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Give an exam , say:",
    "options": [
      "Prepare",
      "Improve",
      "Pull off the bandage",
      "Take an exam"
    ],
    "answer": "Take an exam"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Pass time , say:",
    "options": [
      "Spend time",
      "Deliver a speech",
      "Pull off the bandage",
      "Smile"
    ],
    "answer": "Spend time"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Return back , say:",
    "options": [
      "Return",
      "Go jogging",
      "Take off clothes",
      "Ask for permission"
    ],
    "answer": "Return"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Discuss about , say:",
    "options": [
      "Discuss",
      "Build a relationship",
      "Make noise",
      "Draw a sketch"
    ],
    "answer": "Discuss"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Revert back , say:",
    "options": [
      "Arrive at the office",
      "Reply",
      "Take off clothes",
      "Scrape off paint"
    ],
    "answer": "Reply"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do a job , say:",
    "options": [
      "Work",
      "Make a call",
      "Learn",
      "Go outside"
    ],
    "answer": "Work"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Say lies , say:",
    "options": [
      "Check out / Look over",
      "Tell lies",
      "Get some rest",
      "Repeat the mistake"
    ],
    "answer": "Tell lies"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Speak truth , say:",
    "options": [
      "Meditate",
      "Go outside",
      "Act",
      "Tell the truth"
    ],
    "answer": "Tell the truth"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do party , say:",
    "options": [
      "Throw a party",
      "Turn on the light",
      "Wear clothes",
      "Get some rest"
    ],
    "answer": "Throw a party"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Give a speech , say:",
    "options": [
      "Attend an interview",
      "Apply makeup",
      "File a complaint",
      "Deliver a speech"
    ],
    "answer": "Deliver a speech"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Cut the call , say:",
    "options": [
      "Take a test",
      "Cause pain",
      "Take a test",
      "Hang up"
    ],
    "answer": "Hang up"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Join the job , say:",
    "options": [
      "Take an exam",
      "Take an exam",
      "Start work",
      "Tell the truth"
    ],
    "answer": "Start work"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do jogging , say:",
    "options": [
      "Turn on the light",
      "Apply makeup",
      "Go jogging",
      "Come inside"
    ],
    "answer": "Go jogging"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do swimming , say:",
    "options": [
      "Go jogging",
      "Make a decision",
      "Go swimming",
      "Throw a party"
    ],
    "answer": "Go swimming"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Go for shopping , say:",
    "options": [
      "Have a bath",
      "Hurry back",
      "Wipe off stains",
      "Go shopping"
    ],
    "answer": "Go shopping"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Come to office , say:",
    "options": [
      "Show respect",
      "Arrive at the office",
      "Make noise",
      "Make efforts"
    ],
    "answer": "Arrive at the office"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do progress , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make progress",
      "Sign",
      "Have dinner",
      "Go shopping"
    ],
    "answer": "Make progress"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take rest , say:",
    "options": [
      "Spend time",
      "Hurry back",
      "Check out / Look over",
      "Get some rest"
    ],
    "answer": "Get some rest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Give a test , say:",
    "options": [
      "File a complaint",
      "Take a test",
      "Have a rest",
      "Deliver a speech"
    ],
    "answer": "Take a test"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take revenge , say:",
    "options": [
      "Tell the truth",
      "Get revenge",
      "Go shopping",
      "Smile"
    ],
    "answer": "Get revenge"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Come back fast , say:",
    "options": [
      "Tell the truth",
      "Hurry back",
      "Fulfill the need",
      "Register"
    ],
    "answer": "Hurry back"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do a phone call , say:",
    "options": [
      "Smile",
      "Clean up",
      "Make a phone call",
      "Show interest"
    ],
    "answer": "Make a phone call"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take a decision , say:",
    "options": [
      "Clean up",
      "Complete homework",
      "Have dinner",
      "Make a decision"
    ],
    "answer": "Make a decision"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Make a party , say:",
    "options": [
      "Register",
      "Host a party",
      "Have a rest",
      "Have a bath"
    ],
    "answer": "Host a party"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do noise , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make noise",
      "Work",
      "Ask a question",
      "Repeat the mistake"
    ],
    "answer": "Make noise"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do a plan , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make a plan",
      "Turn off the light",
      "Take a picture",
      "Go jogging"
    ],
    "answer": "Make a plan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Go to outside , say:",
    "options": [
      "Go outside",
      "Take off clothes",
      "Work",
      "React"
    ],
    "answer": "Go outside"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Come to inside , say:",
    "options": [
      "Have lunch",
      "File a complaint",
      "Come inside",
      "Discuss"
    ],
    "answer": "Come inside"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do brushing , say:",
    "options": [
      "Brush your teeth",
      "Turn on the light",
      "Make progress",
      "Have a bath"
    ],
    "answer": "Brush your teeth"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take a breakfast , say:",
    "options": [
      "Have breakfast",
      "Take a test",
      "Throw a party",
      "Tease"
    ],
    "answer": "Have breakfast"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take a lunch , say:",
    "options": [
      "Have lunch",
      "Take an exam",
      "Have breakfast",
      "Complete homework"
    ],
    "answer": "Have lunch"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take a dinner , say:",
    "options": [
      "Take a test",
      "Spend time",
      "Have dinner",
      "Throw a party"
    ],
    "answer": "Have dinner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Put a question , say:",
    "options": [
      "Arrive at the office",
      "Grab food",
      "Ask a question",
      "Deliver a speech"
    ],
    "answer": "Ask a question"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Give pain , say:",
    "options": [
      "Cause pain",
      "Tell lies",
      "Tell the truth",
      "Make noise"
    ],
    "answer": "Cause pain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take a bath , say:",
    "options": [
      "Have a bath",
      "Work out",
      "Apologize",
      "Make noise"
    ],
    "answer": "Have a bath"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take a shower , say:",
    "options": [
      "Go swimming",
      "Have a shower",
      "Make a promise",
      "Pull out the nail"
    ],
    "answer": "Have a shower"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Make friends , say:",
    "options": [
      "Take a test",
      "Turn on the light",
      "Turn off the light",
      "Become friends"
    ],
    "answer": "Become friends"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do fun , say:",
    "options": [
      "Plan",
      "Offer a gift",
      "Make a payment",
      "Have fun"
    ],
    "answer": "Have fun"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do the cleaning , say:",
    "options": [
      "Clean up",
      "Go outside",
      "Sign",
      "Make a mistake"
    ],
    "answer": "Clean up"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Put clothes , say:",
    "options": [
      "Wear clothes",
      "Reply",
      "Speak up",
      "Cause pain"
    ],
    "answer": "Wear clothes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Remove clothes , say:",
    "options": [
      "Log out the password",
      "Speak up",
      "Take off clothes",
      "Pull off the bandage"
    ],
    "answer": "Take off clothes"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do a complaint , say:",
    "options": [
      "Peek at",
      "Discuss",
      "Fulfill the need",
      "File a complaint"
    ],
    "answer": "File a complaint"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Say sorry , say:",
    "options": [
      "Clean up",
      "Apologize",
      "Ask for help",
      "Become friends"
    ],
    "answer": "Apologize"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do a promise , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make a mistake",
      "Register",
      "Take an exam",
      "Make a promise"
    ],
    "answer": "Make a promise"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do exercise , say:",
    "options": [
      "Work out",
      "Take a picture",
      "Return",
      "Host a party"
    ],
    "answer": "Work out"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do meditation , say:",
    "options": [
      "Host a party",
      "Meditate",
      "Plan",
      "Brush your teeth"
    ],
    "answer": "Meditate"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do investment , say:",
    "options": [
      "Tell a lie",
      "Make efforts",
      "Attend class",
      "Invest"
    ],
    "answer": "Invest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do the needful , say:",
    "options": [
      "Take revenge",
      "Peek at",
      "Take necessary action",
      "Wash off dirt"
    ],
    "answer": "Take necessary action"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take tension , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make an effort",
      "Worry",
      "Peel off the sticker",
      "Make a decision"
    ],
    "answer": "Worry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Get sleep , say:",
    "options": [
      "Fall asleep",
      "Shut down (a machine)",
      "Take an exam",
      "Pop off the lid"
    ],
    "answer": "Fall asleep"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Make relationship , say:",
    "options": [
      "Smile",
      "Fall asleep",
      "Return",
      "Build a relationship"
    ],
    "answer": "Build a relationship"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do a sketch , say:",
    "options": [
      "Worry",
      "Draw a sketch",
      "Make a payment",
      "Have fun"
    ],
    "answer": "Draw a sketch"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do makeup , say:",
    "options": [
      "Attend class",
      "Apply makeup",
      "Scrape off paint",
      "Make a mistake"
    ],
    "answer": "Apply makeup"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do a call , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make a call",
      "Glance at",
      "Pop off the lid",
      "Hang up"
    ],
    "answer": "Make a call"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do mistake , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make a mistake",
      "Arrive at the office",
      "Brush off the dust",
      "Take an exam"
    ],
    "answer": "Make a mistake"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do shopping , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make a mistake",
      "Work",
      "Go shopping",
      "Have a rest"
    ],
    "answer": "Go shopping"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Give exam , say:",
    "options": [
      "Learn",
      "Take necessary action",
      "Take an exam",
      "Attend class"
    ],
    "answer": "Take an exam"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Give test , say:",
    "options": [
      "Take a test",
      "Give news",
      "Have breakfast",
      "Attend class"
    ],
    "answer": "Take a test"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do homework , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make a decision",
      "Make a plan",
      "Complete homework",
      "Have a dream"
    ],
    "answer": "Complete homework"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take decision , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make progress",
      "Make a decision",
      "Improve",
      "Complete homework"
    ],
    "answer": "Make a decision"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Give advice , say:",
    "options": [
      "Get revenge",
      "Move out furniture",
      "Make a decision",
      "Offer advice"
    ],
    "answer": "Offer advice"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do duty , say:",
    "options": [
      "Perform duty",
      "Take a test",
      "Clean up",
      "Reply"
    ],
    "answer": "Perform duty"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take photo , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make a call",
      "Go shopping",
      "Make a decision",
      "Take a picture"
    ],
    "answer": "Take a picture"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take rest , say:",
    "options": [
      "Get some rest",
      "Make a mistake",
      "Take out the garbage",
      "Glare at"
    ],
    "answer": "Get some rest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Give a gift , say:",
    "options": [
      "Have a rest",
      "Throw a party",
      "Reply",
      "Offer a gift"
    ],
    "answer": "Offer a gift"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do business , say:",
    "options": [
      "Meditate",
      "Run a business",
      "Work",
      "Arrive at the office"
    ],
    "answer": "Run a business"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do job , say:",
    "options": [
      "Pull off the bandage",
      "Make a decision",
      "Work a job",
      "Look after"
    ],
    "answer": "Work a job"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Give interview , say:",
    "options": [
      "Scrape off paint",
      "Attend an interview",
      "Prepare",
      "Go shopping"
    ],
    "answer": "Attend an interview"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Give example , say:",
    "options": [
      "Ask for help",
      "Show respect",
      "Cause pain",
      "Provide an example"
    ],
    "answer": "Provide an example"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Put attention , say:",
    "options": [
      "Pay attention",
      "Build a relationship",
      "Go shopping",
      "Work"
    ],
    "answer": "Pay attention"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do efforts , say:",
    "options": [
      "Take necessary action",
      "File a complaint",
      "Book (a seat, hotel, etc.)",
      "Make efforts"
    ],
    "answer": "Make efforts"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take permission , say:",
    "options": [
      "Take a test",
      "Brush your teeth",
      "Make a plan",
      "Ask for permission"
    ],
    "answer": "Ask for permission"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Make fun of , say:",
    "options": [
      "Look after",
      "Tease",
      "Get some rest",
      "Take an exam"
    ],
    "answer": "Tease"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do mistake again , say:",
    "options": [
      "Tell lies",
      "Make a call",
      "Make progress",
      "Repeat the mistake"
    ],
    "answer": "Repeat the mistake"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do copy , say:",
    "options": [
      "Cheat or Copy",
      "Take a photo",
      "Make a mistake",
      "Work out"
    ],
    "answer": "Cheat or Copy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Give respect , say:",
    "options": [
      "Fall asleep",
      "Show respect",
      "File a complaint",
      "Take an exam"
    ],
    "answer": "Show respect"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Make smile , say:",
    "options": [
      "Spend time",
      "Smile",
      "Complete homework",
      "Make a mistake"
    ],
    "answer": "Smile"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take help , say:",
    "options": [
      "Ask for help",
      "Give news",
      "Fulfill the need",
      "Log out the password"
    ],
    "answer": "Ask for help"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Put signature , say:",
    "options": [
      "Wear clothes",
      "Hurry back",
      "Brush off the dust",
      "Sign"
    ],
    "answer": "Sign"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do registration , say:",
    "options": [
      "Reply",
      "Brush off the dust",
      "Register",
      "Make an effort"
    ],
    "answer": "Register"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do booking , say:",
    "options": [
      "Go shopping",
      "Take necessary action",
      "Book (a seat, hotel, etc.)",
      "Have dinner"
    ],
    "answer": "Book (a seat, hotel, etc.)"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do payment , say:",
    "options": [
      "Complete homework",
      "Host a party",
      "Make a payment",
      "Make noise"
    ],
    "answer": "Make a payment"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take class , say:",
    "options": [
      "Attend class",
      "Make a decision",
      "Register",
      "Make arrangements"
    ],
    "answer": "Attend class"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take interest , say:",
    "options": [
      "Speak up",
      "Clean up",
      "Get revenge",
      "Show interest"
    ],
    "answer": "Show interest"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do arrangements , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make arrangements",
      "Make efforts",
      "Take necessary action",
      "Make a plan"
    ],
    "answer": "Make arrangements"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take action , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make a plan",
      "Show interest",
      "Pay attention",
      "Act"
    ],
    "answer": "Act"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do improvement , say:",
    "options": [
      "Have fun",
      "Make a decision",
      "Make progress",
      "Improve"
    ],
    "answer": "Improve"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Make revenge , say:",
    "options": [
      "Have breakfast",
      "Make progress",
      "Take revenge",
      "Turn on the light"
    ],
    "answer": "Take revenge"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do planning , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make noise",
      "Go shopping",
      "Take necessary action",
      "Plan"
    ],
    "answer": "Plan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do progress , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make progress",
      "Work out",
      "Have a dream",
      "Pay attention"
    ],
    "answer": "Make progress"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Take care of , say:",
    "options": [
      "Look after",
      "Run a business",
      "Throw a party",
      "Work"
    ],
    "answer": "Look after"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Do the need , say:",
    "options": [
      "Make a phone call",
      "Fall asleep",
      "Cause pain",
      "Fulfill the need"
    ],
    "answer": "Fulfill the need"
  },
  {
    "question": "Do not say: Give reaction , say:",
    "options": [
      "React",
      "Come inside",
      "Tease",
      "Grab food"
    ],
    "answer": "React"
  }
]